{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/51622935","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622935","name":"Cenaduria Y Taqueria Triangulo Dorado","address":"8065 W. Vernor","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Adrian Torres","licenseNumber":"238144","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.12836,42.31072","geojson":{"id":"51622935","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.128355857,42.310722385]},"properties":{"name":"Cenaduria Y Taqueria Triangulo Dorado","owner":"Adrian Torres","address":"8065 W. Vernor","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"238144","establishmentid":"51622935","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2019-03-04"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4141","name":"Latino's Cafe","address":"8065 W.Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3414","name":"Al-Andaleeb Restaurant","address":"8020 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"1730","name":"Great Panda Garden Chinese Restaurant","address":"7930 Vernor St. W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"565","name":"La Mexicana Restaruant","address":"7928 Vernor W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"926","name":"Bennett Elementary","address":"2111 Mullane St.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"2294","name":"Spring at Vernor Coney Island","address":"7900 Vernor St. W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4471","name":"Dave's Famous Coney Island & Grill","address":"7900 Vernor, W.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1225","name":"Pizza Di Casa","address":"2134 Springwells Ave.","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51622723","name":"Vitamin Juice ","address":"2030 Springwells","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"211","name":"La Terraza","address":"8445 Vernor St.W.","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60573","inspectionDate":"2022-08-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Cease and Desist","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"56817","inspectionDate":"2021-12-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Cease and Desist","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"54827","inspectionDate":"2021-05-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-202.18","violationDescription":"(A) SHELLSTOCK shall be obtained in containers bearing legible source      identification tags or labels that are affixed by the harvester or DEALER that      depurates, ships, or reships the SHELLSTOCK, as specified in the National      Shellfish Sanitation Program Guide for the Control of Molluscan Shellfish, and      that list: (Pf)  \n(1) Except as specified under ¶ (C) of this section, on the harvester's tag or label,     the following information in the following order: (Pf)\n(a) The harvester's identification number that is assigned by the SHELLFISH             CONTROL AUTHORITY, (Pf)\n(b) The date of harvesting, (Pf)\n(c) The most precise identification of the harvest location or aquaculture site that       is practicable based on the system of harvest area designations that is in           use by the SHELLFISH CONTROL AUTHORITY and including the           abbreviation of the name of the state or country in which the shellfish are           harvested, (Pf)\n(d) The type and quantity of shellfish, (Pf) and\n(e) The following statement in bold, capitalized type: \"This tag is required to be         attached until container is empty or retagged and thereafter kept on file for 90           days\"; (Pf) and\n(2) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, on each DEALER'S tag or label, the following information in the following order: (Pf)\n(a) The DEALER'S name and address, and the CERTIFICATION NUMBER           assigned by the SHELLFISH CONTROL AUTHORITY, (Pf)\n(b) The original shipper's CERTIFICATION NUMBER including the abbreviation of the name of the state or country in which the shellfish are harvested, (Pf)\n(c) The same information as specified for a harvester's tag under Subparagraphs       (A)(1)(b)-(d) of this section,(Pf) and\n(d) The following statement in bold, capitalized type: \"This tag is required to be         attached until container is empty and thereafter kept on file for 90 days.\" (Pf)  \n(B) A container of shellstock that does not bear a tag or label or that bears a tag or   label that does not contain all the information as specified under ¶ (A) of this      section shall be subject to a hold order, as allowed by law, or seizure and      destruction in accordance with 21 CFR Subpart D - Specific Administrative      Decisions Regarding Interstate Shipments, Section 1240.60(d).   \n(C) If a place is provided on the harvester's tag or label for a dealer's name, address,  and certification number, the dealer's information shall be listed first.   \n(D) If the harvester's tag or label is designed to accommodate each dealer's      identification as specified under Subparagraphs (A)(2)(a) and (b) of this section,      individual dealer tags or labels need not be provided.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Shellstock","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Tag(s)","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"SHELL FISH TAGS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-05-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.6141","violationDescription":"Sec. 6141. (1) A food service establishment in which solid foods are sold and consumed on the premises shall prominently display a poster in the kitchen area of the food service establishment diagramming and explaining the antichoking techniques safe for both adults and children approved by the department for dislodging foreign obstacles caught in the throat of a choking person.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"SIGNAGE","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53124","inspectionDate":"2020-10-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.5101","violationDescription":"(1) A person shall not do or cause to be done any of the following:  (a) Manufacture, sell, deliver,  hold, or offer for sale adulterated or misbranded food.    (b) Adulterate or misbrand food.    (c) Receive in commerce food that is adulterated  or misbranded and deliver or proffer the delivery of that food for pay or  otherwise.    (d) Sell, deliver for sale, hold for sale, or  offer for sale food unless that person holds a license issued under chapter IV.    (e) Disseminate a false advertisement concerning food or a food establishment.    (f) Refuse to permit entry or evaluation, or to  permit the taking of a sample, as authorized by section 2111.    (g) Give a false guaranty or undertaking concerning food, unless in good-faith reliance on a guaranty or undertaking to the same effect signed  by and containing the name and address of the person from whom the food was received.    (h) Remove or dispose of seized or embargoed  food in violation of section 2105.    (i) Alter, mutilate, destroy, obliterate, or  remove all or part of the label or do any other act with respect to a food  while the food is held for sale resulting in the food being adulterated or  misbranded.    (j) Forge, counterfeit, simulate, or falsely  represent, or without proper authority use any mark, stamp, tag, label, or  other identification device authorized or required by this act or rules.    (k) Permit filthy or insanitary conditions to  exist in a food establishment in which food intended for human consumption is  manufactured, received, kept, stored, served, sold, or offered for sale.    (l)  Falsely identify a country, state, or other place of origin of food on a label,  tag, or other document with intent to deceive or defraud.    (m) Fail to establish or maintain any record or  make any report required under this act or the federal act, or refuse to permit  access to or verification or copying of any such required record.    (n) Interfere with the director in the conduct  of his or her responsibilities under this act.    (o) Make a false statement, representation, or  certification in any application, report, plan, or other document that is  required to be maintained under this act or rules.    (p) Remove a tag, seal, or mark placed by the  director.    (q) Operate without a license, registration,  permit, or endorsement.    (r) Violate a provision of this act or a rule.    (s) Operate as a shellfish dealer without a shellfish dealer certificate.    (t) If the person is a food establishment, permit Michigan bridge card access to food assistance program benefits unless the food establishment's inventory records match redemption files for Michigan bridge card usage for food assistance program benefits and 1 or more of the following apply:     (i) The food for sale includes, on a continuous basis, at least 3 varieties of foods in each of the following 4 staple food groups and perishable foods in at least 2 of the groups:      (A) Meat, poultry, or fish.      (B) Bread or cereal.     (C)   Vegetables or fruits.     (D) Dairy products.     (ii) At least 50% of the total dollar amount of all retail sales, including food and nonfood items, fuel, and services at the food establishment is from the sale of food in any of the 4 staple food groups.  (2) Each day a violation of this section occurs is a separate violation of this section.      ","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Test strips","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"Without use of trapping devices","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"PESTS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize trapping devices to help eliminate pests."},{"violationCode":"2-101.11","violationDescription":"A PERSON IN CHARGE shall be present in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT during all hours of operation. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not present","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-10-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"A Person in Charge is required to be present during all hours of operation."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Self-closing device","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"3-305.12","violationDescription":"FOOD may not be stored:\n(A)  In locker rooms;\n(B)  In toilet rooms;\n(C)  In dressing rooms;\n(D)  In garbage rooms;\n(E)  In mechanical rooms;\n(F)  Under sewer lines that are not shielded to intercept potential drips;\n(G)  Under leaking water lines, including leaking automatic fire sprinkler heads, or        under lines on which water has condensed;\n(H)  Under open stairwells; or\n(I)   Under other sources of contamination.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food(s) stored","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In prohibited area(s)","subProblem":"In or under other sources of contamination","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Food Storage","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"49818","inspectionDate":"2019-11-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Hose(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Test strips","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"COOLING METHODS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"3-203.12","violationDescription":"SHELLSTOCK tags shall remain attached to the container in which the shellstock are received until the container is empty and tags shall be retained for 90 days after the container is empty.  Retained tags shall be kept in chronological order and correlated to the date when shellstock are harvested. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Shellstock","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Identification","subProblem":"Tag(s) not retained for 90 days","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"SHELL FISH TAGS","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Retain on file"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In water less than 135 degrees f","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Dispensing utensil","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain water at 135 degrees F or greater."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Food Storage","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"5-203.13","violationDescription":"At least 1 service sink or 1 curbed cleaning facility equipped with a floor drain shall be provided and conveniently located for the cleaning of mops or similar wet floor cleaning tools and for the disposal of mop water and similar liquid waste.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mop/utility sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Mop sink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"Door - back door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Covered waste container","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"45961","inspectionDate":"2019-04-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Other chemical sanitizing solution concentration(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"Sanitizer","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\n\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Glove usage","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Handwashing soap","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-05-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Screening that is sixteen mesh to the inch or greater","location":"FRONT DOOR","subLocation":"Openings","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Ceiling (s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Covered waste container","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Light Shield(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622935"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}